{
    "subject": "resource/Susan_Saint_James",
    "predicate": "ontology/spouse",
    "object": "resource/Dick_Ebersol",
    "human_readable": "Susan Saint James was married to Dick Ebersol.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886314272880554,
            "question": "Was Dick Ebersol married to Susan Saint James?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9268848299980164,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Susan Saint James and Dick Ebersol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227302670478821,
            "question": "Who was Susan Saint James married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7799655795097351,
            "question": "Are there any famous people connected to Susan Saint James or Dick Ebersol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7406241297721863,
            "question": "Who is Susan Saint James?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6640389561653137,
            "question": "Do Susan Saint James and Dick Ebersol have any children together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6484600901603699,
            "question": "Who is Dick Ebersol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40470090508461,
            "question": "What is Dick Ebersol known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34870901703834534,
            "question": "What are some of Susan Saint James' notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33196720480918884,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Susan Saint James' personal life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Susan Saint James was married to Dick Ebersol.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4111_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Susan Saint James' notable works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4111_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Dick Ebersol known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4111_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Dick Ebersol?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4111_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4111_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Susan Saint James has been happily married to television executive Dick Ebersol for over three decades, and provide specific dates and details about their relationship (e.g., they were dating for 1 month after getting together in Oct 1981 and were married on 21st Nov 1981). This information confirms the triple that Susan Saint James was married to Dick Ebersol."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Susan Saint James has been married to Dick Ebersol for over 35 years and provide specific details about their marriage, including the date they were married (November 21, 1981), as well as information on their children."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}